Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(Episode 4)
You couldn't even keep an eye on a blind person.
Things could've been bad.
Greetings, Your Highness.
My naughty daughter...
has caused you trouble.
Father, what are you saying?
My dear.
If you don't want to go back to the manor,
I won't force you.
You can write a letter to the Lu family head in Jiangnan...
and ask him...
to transfer me the Lu family's fortune.
I might be able...
to grant you a divorce.
Dream on.
Don't blame me...
for not going easy on you, then.
Bao Qin!
- Bao Qin. - Don't move.
How bold of your maid...
to trespass...
the Jingzhao Magistrate Office.
Do you know...
who the magistrate...
works for?
You've gone too far.
Ms. Lu Zhao.
Don't worry about me.
The Lu family property is the ancestral inheritance...
left to you by the old master and madam.
You can't give it to this thief!
Bao Qin!
Bao Qin.
Why?
Why did you do this?
Bao Qin.
Mother.
Father.
Uncle hit me.
Uncle.
How could you hit your daughter so hard?
Xue Er. It's my fault.
Don't be mad at me.
"Daughter"?
All of you...
Tell me.
How did you...
regain your vision?
The gods opened my eyes...
so that I could see...
your true colors, you demons.
You wench.
You're still stubborn even in the face of death.
Lu Zhao.
If gods existed,
you wouldn't have ended up like this.
Just write the letter.
I'll give you...
a chance to live.
All right?
Even if I die,
I won't let you have your way.
You don't know what's good for you.
I see you want to do this the hard way.
Lu Zhao.
Why are you doing this?
You're pregnant.
Do you want this child...
to die without ever seeing the world?
What has the child done wrong?
You're right.
I'm with child.
Here.
Write the letter.
Sign and seal it.
I'll make sure you and your son...
are safe.
Untie me.
Your Highness.
Hurry.
Summon the doctor.
Summon the doctor!
Yes.
I won't be able to control her without the child.
Situ Xian.
You're extremely cruel.
With your blood running through it,
this child may one day become a menace.
You don't deserve to have my child.
Don't even think...
about using him to control the Lu family.
Wench.
It turns out...
you've planned it all out.
You wench!
Doctor.
Doctor!
Where's the doctor?
Your Highness.
The rouge you put on yourself...
is not red enough.
Let's see.
It's just right.
What's wrong?
Are you unhappy with the rouge I helped you apply?
I forgot.
I'm sorry.
You were given mute poison.
You can't talk.
Even if you're not happy with it,
you have to put up with it.
The guests will be here soon.
Once the shackles are off,
your birthday banquet...
will begin.
After today,
if His Highness doesn't get your handwritten letter,
the lives of the Lu family...
will be in danger.
Lu Zhao.
You'd better...
behave yourself.
Sis.
I know everything.
You and I are not twins by blood.
Judging by the time,
I'm actually your older brother.
You've always protected me.
Let me protect you this time.
Don't worry.
For every drop of blood you shed,
and every pain you've suffered,
I'll make them pay a thousandfold.
No one can separate us.
Not even death.
The revival spell needs to be performed personally.
You need to use your blood...
to attract her soul.
If this works,
a blood-colored orchid will appear on her body...
to signal her soul's return.
But this spell defies Heaven and alters fate.
Whether you succeed or not,
you'll have to pay a huge price.
You can have no regrets, come life or death.
Have you made up your mind?
If I can get my sister back,
so what if I die?
Let's begin.
I pay my respects, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Rumor has it...
that Her Highness is not of high birth...
and is blind.
Despite that, you treat her like a treasure.
Now, to celebrate her birthday,
you've built Zhaoyue Pavilion.
You really are...
the most devoted lover in Ying.
Everyone.
Please don't tease me.
I'm ashamed to say this.
My dear caught a cold today.
She lost her voice temporarily.
It's my fault...
for not taking good care of her.
Your Highness.
Her Highness has arrived.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Thank you, Ms. Liu.
Don't make me break your legs.
Start walking.
Everyone.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers, my dear.
We pay our respects, Your Highness.
It's a happy occasion.
Officials.
The Prince of Chu is plotting a rebellion.
To steal the Lu family's assets,
he has raised an army... and harmed me.
Today,
I'm risking my life...
to seek an audience with His Majesty.
I hope all of you can help me.
I poisoned her mute myself.
How can she still talk?
Go on.
I, Xiao Ren, made a vow...
to help me bring Sis back to life.
I'm willing to pay any price.
If any of you gods refuse,
I'll lay waste to every temple...
and crush every sacred statue.
Situ Xian...
attempted rebellion.
That's high treason.
Are you just going to turn a blind eye to it?
Say something.
Say something!
Lu Zhao.
His Highness prepared this birthday banquet for you.
Do you think...
anyone could get in...
if they weren't His Highness' trusted aides?
You’re so stupid it’s pathetic.
You're disobedient.
You should know this.
Those who don't listen...
have to pay the price.
Situ Xian.
You bastard. What are you trying to do?
I'm trying to teach you a lesson.
The hundred lives...
in the Lu family...
lie in your hands.
You know...
after I turn 18,
I'll inherit the Lu family's assets.
What you don't know...
is that if I die,
all the Lu family's assets...
will be handed over to the state treasury.
With such merits,
how dare you lay a finger on my family?
What are you doing?
Your Highness.
Go after her!
Supreme Celestial Altar,
unceasing in all change.
May the three souls endure forever,
the spirit remain unbroken.
Talismans, heed my command.
Soul,
return!